reallovesexdolls.com 2018-10-20

# Real Love Sex Dolls Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

At RealLoveSexDolls.com , we are dedicated to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect is that which you voluntarily provide to us. We may collect information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information when you register as a user on our website, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. We use this information to personalize and enhance your experience, improve customer service on the website, as a means to contact you if necessary, to tailor loyalty programs, to provide periodic electronic correspondence and to fulfill your orders and process transactions efficiently. We never sell or share your personal information.

Security

We use a secure server to maintain the safety of your personal information. Information that you submit via the website is protected with industry standard SSL encryption technology, designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

We use administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard personal information against loss, theft and unauthorised  uses, access or modifications. Certain areas of our web sites may be password protected. If you are a user of our web sites and have a password, you can help to preserve your privacy by ensuring that you do not share your password with anyone else. 

Payments made via our web sites are processed in a secure environment using software provided by PayPal or other third party providers.   
We take steps to regularly validate the personal information we hold to ensure that the information is accurate and, where necessary, up to date. Information that is no longer required for any valid business purpose, and that we are not required to keep pursuant to any applicable law, will be routinely destroyed by secure means.

Cookies

A web cookie, a commonly used data collection technology, is simply a piece of text which can be placed on the browser of your personal computer or mobile device and subsequently read as you visit a web site. We use cookies and similar technologies on our web sites to improve performance and make your experience better. No personally identifiable information is linked to enabling use of cookies, and the cookie is terminated upon closing the browser until the user returns to the site.

The cookies we use or allow are an accepted part of ecommerce and important to your use of our web sites. Performance cookies allow us to understand our audiences as a whole and improve how our sites meet your needs and expectations. Many of the functional cookies are basic to how our sites and services work. The cookies we use for registration allow us to conduct our business online. Our sites and services, or parts of them, may not work properly without these cookies.
